

Theodore

Contact

Address Taunggyi, Shan State, Myanmar.

Phone 09891672344

Email theodoreoovoo@gmail.com

Skills

Skilled in Microsoft Office
Office operations
Accounting
Web development Technologies
Software development
Adobe Creative Suite
IT Engineer
Linux
Networking
Basic of Ethical Hacking

I attended the basic and middle School in Kayah State, Myanmar. After that I attended English Academic 1 and 2 in Thailand. As the same time, I work as a translator and office staff in there. After that I came back to Myanmar to attend Diploma in Web development and Diploma in software Engineering in Y-Max University, Yangon, Myanmar. As the same time, I worked as computer teacher and computer maintain in Thamoas Aquinas' Learning Centre, Loikaw, Kayah State.

Work History

2016-2019 Office Staff & English Translator

Migrate School, Mae Sot, Thailand.

I worked as a English Translator and office staff. Sometime, I teach children basic computer.

2020-2021 Computer Teacher and Computer maintain in

Loikaw, Kayah State.

Education

2017-2018 Academic English 1 & 2

(Thabyay Education Network)

2020-2021 Diploma in Web Development (NCFE,UK)

Diploma in Software Engineer (NCFE,UK)

Certifications

Diploma in Web development (NCFE,UK)

Diploma in Software Engineer (NCFE,UK)

DTP (ANS computer training center)

Graphic Design (ANS computer training center)

Programming Languages (Udemy.com)

Accounting (Udemy.com)

Networking (Y-max university, Udemy.com)

Linux (Y-max university, Udemy.com)

Basic of Ethical Hacking (Udemy.com)